<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Caren Elhenawy&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Caren Elhenawy&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best of Both Worlds, huh?</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/09/new-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/09/new-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>You ever wish you had the best of both worlds? Well now you cam with reticulate! R Studio and Python are both excellent softwares and often concieved as rivals. If you ask anyone in the data science field, they either say they are Team R Studio or Team Python. Why can&#39;t they be Team Both? With reticulate, now you can! If those in Team R Studio are unfamilar with Python, Python can pretty much complete the same tasks as R Studio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caren - Project 2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>My data is revolved around the vitals of individuals that could be at risk for heart complications. The dataset contains their age, sex, chest pain level, resting blood pressure, chlorestrol levels, maximum heart rate, and if they have excercise induced angina. There is a total of 7 variables and 58 observations. The categorical variable is the chest pain variable. There are four groups. The individual reports that they either have mild, moderate, severe, or no chest pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>For this project, I chose to focus on mental health and the resources available in countries worldwide. The first dataset contains the suicide rates of 4 different years from each country. The suicide rates are for both genders combined and are age-standardized. The second dataset contains the amount of mental health specialitists present in the same countries during the year 2016. Each of the values in the second dataset, excluding the year, was per a population of 100000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>  Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
